A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Advanced Medical Fellowships, SG 1, Series 3 FA275
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Foreign Fellowships, 1941-1980; 3
  - Staikopoulou, Tia, May 16, 1950-March 3, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 754)
  - Stewart, F. S., December 16, 1964-January 5, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 755)
  - Stokes, John Fisher, December 16, 1964-December 14, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 756)
  - Strom, Gunnar, December 16, 1965 to June 13, 1966; December 28, 1970 to January 13, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 757)
  - Stuart, Kenneth L., January 16, 1964-May 6, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 758)
  - Sumi, Taeko, April 27, 1955 to October 9, 1959; December 3, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 759)
  - Sutherland, Gordon, May 27, 1948-October 17, 1949 (Box 63, Folder 760)
  - Tabbara, Riad A., August 8, 1955-January 22, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 761)
  - Tamayo, Ruy Perez, October 23, 1963-April 13, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 762)
  - Toussieng, Povl, January 13, 1951-February 5, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 763)
  - Turnbull, Adam L., January 13, 1961-September 20, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 764)
  - Vendelboe, Jonna, January 16, 1952-February 2, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 765)
  - Vilkki, Panu, February 24, 1967-November 21, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 766)
  - Vourikoski, Irja, April 9, 1953-November 12, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 767)
  - Vyas, Bal Krishan, April 19, 1954 to May 31, 1956; July 7, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 768)
  - Waller, Doris, October 12, 1951-January 2, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 769)
  - Wheeldon, Constance Joy, March 25, 1949-September 17, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 770)
  - Whyte, Marion B. H., July 3, 1957-October 15, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 771)
  - Whitfield, A. G. W., October 4, 1961-November 13, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 772)
  - Whitteridge, David, September 21, 1959-January 13, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 773)
  - Wilenski, Peter, April 25, 1969-June 7, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 774)
  - Williams, Robert J. P., January 21, 1966-October 13, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 775)
  - Wilson, Alastair M. M., January 30, 1962-May 12, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 776)
  - Winstanley, John M. B., December 16, 1964-February 4, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 777)
  - Winton, F. R., November 21, 1950-September 6, 1951 (Box 64, Folder 778)
  - Withers, Ronald F. J., April 22, 1966-February 14, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 779)
  - Witts, Leslie John, June 2, 1966-May 2, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 780)
- Institutional Block Grants, 1948-1979; 4
  The material in this subseries is arranged alphabetically by institution. The material within each institution's file is arranged chronologically.
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine, June 29, 1962-December 16, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 781)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine, June 29, 1962-December 16, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 782)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine, June 29, 1962-December 16, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 783)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine, June 29, 1962-December 16, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 784)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine, June 29, 1962-December 16, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 785)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine, June 29, 1962-December 16, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 786)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine, February 9, 1972-September 21, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 787)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine, February 9, 1972-September 21, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 788)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, May 5, 1954-June 3, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 789)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., October 15, 1954-August 2, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 790)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., October 15, 1954-August 2, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 791)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., October 15, 1954-August 2, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 792)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., October 15, 1954-August 2, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 793)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., October 15, 1954-August 2, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 794)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., October 15, 1954-August 2, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 795)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., October 15, 1954-August 2, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 796)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., September 6, 1957-October 5, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 797)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., September 6, 1957-October 5, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 798)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., September 6, 1957-October 5, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 799)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., September 6, 1957-October 5, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 800)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., September 6, 1957-October 5, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 801)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., September 6, 1957-October 5, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 802)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., September 6, 1957-October 5, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 803)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., September 6, 1957-October 5, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 804)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc., March 1, 1962-November 9, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 805)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc. - Fellowship Awards - Master's (B-W), 1957-1958 (Box 67, Folder 806)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc. - Fellowship Awards - Post-Master's (B-C), 1957-1958 (Box 67, Folder 807)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc. - Fellowship Awards - Post-Master's (D-H), 1957-1958 (Box 67, Folder 808)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc. - Fellowship Awards - Post-Master's (L-S), 1957-1958 (Box 67, Folder 809)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc. - Fellowship Awards - Post-Master's (W-Z), 1957-1958 (Box 67, Folder 810)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc. - Fellowship Awards (B-G), 1960 (Box 67, Folder 811)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc. - Fellowship Awards (H-Z), 1960 (Box 67, Folder 812)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc. - Fellowship Awards (B-L), 1961 (Box 68, Folder 813)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc. - Fellowship Awards (M-Z), 1961 (Box 68, Folder 814)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc. - Fellowship Awards (A-G), 1962 (Box 68, Folder 815)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc. - Fellowship Awards (J-W), 1962 (Box 68, Folder 816)
  - National League for Nursing, Inc. - Letters of Appreciation (A-Z), 1957-1962 (Box 68, Folder 817)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., October 12, 1948-July 3, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 818)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., October 12, 1948-July 3, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 819)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., October 12, 1948-July 3, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 820)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., October 12, 1948-July 3, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 821)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., October 12, 1948-July 3, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 822)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., March 9, 1954-January 19, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 823)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., March 9, 1954-January 19, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 824)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., March 9, 1954-January 19, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 825)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., March 9, 1954-January 19, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 826)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., March 9, 1954-January 19, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 827)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., March 9, 1954-January 19, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 828)
  - Population Council, Inc., November 11, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 829)
    Related Archival Materials note
    See Commonwealth Fund, Grant Series, Box 285, Folders 2715-2716.
  - University of Rochester - Exchange Fellowships, March 26, 1963-September 13, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 830)
  - University of Rochester - Exchange Fellowships, March 26, 1963-September 13, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 831)
  - University of Rochester - Exchange Fellowships, January 13, 1968-December 12, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 832)
  - University of Rochester - Exchange Fellowships, January 13, 1968-December 12, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 833)
  - University of Rochester - Travel Fellowships, March 26, 1963-March 1, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 834)
  - University of the West Indies, January 11, 1960-July 11, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 835)
  - University of the West Indies, January 11, 1960-July 11, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 836)
  - University of the West Indies, January 11, 1960-July 11, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 837)
  - Yale University, November 9, 1953-April 10, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 838)
  - Yale University, November 9, 1953-April 10, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 839)
- Special Awards in Support of Creative Scholarship, 1943-1974; 5
  - Bass, David A., October 20, 1969-March 21, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 840)
  - Cohen, Philip P., June 1, 1956-April 4, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 841)
  - Douglas, Robert M., December 1, 1969-July 6, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 842)
  - French, Joseph H., December 9, 1969-February 1, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 843)
  - Graham, Bob, October 8, 1969-March 2, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 844)
  - Hammon, William McD., June 22, 1956-February 13, 1958 (Box 71, Folder 845)
  - Henderson, Cyril McC., October 4, 1943-May 8, 1944 (Box 71, Folder 846)
  - Loosli, Clayton C., March 7, 1956-April 28, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 847)
  - Parker, Robert F., December 17, 1956-May 9, 1958 (Box 71, Folder 848)
  - Powdermaker, Florence, December 3, 1953-September 28, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 849)
  - Powdermaker, Florence - "The Need to Know", March 15, 1960-October 5, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 850)
  - Seegers, Walter H., May 31, 1956-August 4, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 851)
  - Syverton, Jerome T., June 21, 1956-August 11, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 852)